see this so your man joe biden he wants to let israel basically have complete access to the
stockpile of weapons that are in israel that was provided by america so they could do whatever the
fuck they need to do until this point basically there had to be some type of exchange for them
to be able to dip in he's like you know what y'all can just have it y'all can just have it
me like what they basically just have us by the balls you know how there was like a whole thing
about giving 14.8 billion dollars to israel and then the senate didn't pass it etc
he's like oh you know what i don't even need y'all i'm gonna use my presidentialness to do this
which has a lot of folks saying but you couldn't use your prejudicialness to do a whole lot of other
stuff that you didn't do instead of doing what people are actually asking for which is like
making a ceasefire happen he's actually like nah yes fire yes fire
kamala you good over there because i hope you're not sticking by him